Hello everyone and welcome to This Just In, my name is Marco and I'm here with Scarlett.
Bill!
Scarlett!
Scarlett first.
Come on!
Yay!
Okay, here's Scarlett.
What?
Dude.
The users are going to get really bored by this, so just go with it, Bill.
And uh...
Okay, okay, okay.
We have some exciting news, we have some bad news, we have some good news, we have all
sorts of news.
What's the bad news?
Hit me first with the bad news, Marco.
We actually have two things that are kind of bad news.
Hit me.
Okay.
Give it to me straight.
Hit us.
There's two of us here, Bill.
No, not for long.
Or is that the news?
One of the things is that our friendly voice actor, Scarlett...
Actress!
Oh, sorry.
I am not a dude.
Sorry.
Bad...
Despite popular opinion.
Bad English grammar.
I'm so happy that...
Our very popular English actress...
Thank you.
Scarlett.
Elizabeth.
O'Hara.
Okay, Facebook her.
Scarlett.
Don't!
Anyways, she is actually leaving us.
I am.
Scarlett.
Say it's not true.
She's moving on to greener and better pastures.
Yeah, the co-workers here weren't so hot, Sarah.
So actually, what are you going to be doing now?
I'm going to be working with the expo, actually.
Ah, see.
The big expo in Shanghai.
Otherwise, I wouldn't want to leave Chinese Pod or English Pod.
Okay.
Very good.
See?
Well, we wish you well, Scarlett.
Yeah.
In the bottom of our hearts.
Thank you, Bill.
And you're actually going to be working with some sort of
alcoholic beverage, I understand.
I am.
An Irish brewery company called Porterhouse.
Oh, nice.
So come, come drink our beer.
Will we get free beers?
Yeah.
Will we get free beer?
Yeah, probably.
All users of...
Thanks.
Yeah, just say you're a user of English Pod.
Just say you're a friend of Scarlett.
Just go up to the...
Just mention my name.
Just mention her name.
Awesome.
So that's one of the things that's going on here.
Well, good luck, Scarlett.
Yeah, good luck.
Thank you.
And the other thing is that we had some complaints from some users.
About Scarlett.
That's why I'm leaving, really.
That's why we're letting her go.
Damn it.
Thanks, guys.
No, no, no.
We had a couple of issues with previous lessons.
Like the first, the first dozen lessons that we published, more or less.
And what was going on is that in some parts of the dialogue or in the expansion sentences,
there were some words missing.
There was some sentences that had all the words mixed up.
So we caught on to this and we have fixed it ASAP.
So we have republished this whole technical aspect of it.
It's not that we actually made a mistake, but there was some corruption of the data
and all that technical stuff.
Data is always getting corrupted.
Yes.
We fixed it, though.
So don't worry about it.
Now it's as good as new and you can go check out those first lessons as well.
Yeah.
Okay.
Good work.
Good response time.
It was a close one.
Okay.
So on Monday, we're going to talk about cars.
How much do you know about cars, Scarlett?
Not that much.
So if your car broke down, what would you do?
Well, what, what, I would check the engine.
I checked the petrol monitor to see if I run out of petrol.
Okay.
I'm going to look at it.
I'd open a car bonnet and have a look at it.
Still here.
The car what?
The car bonnet.
Oh, the hood.
I think that's what she's talking about.
The bonnet.
Why is it called a bonnet?
A bonnet is like a hat.
Yeah.
Well, it's kind of like a hat of a car.
Like it's a bonnet.
It's a hood.
But your car isn't a baby.
Yeah.
It's my baby.
Oh, I like this.
My car is my baby.
So what kind of car do you have, Scarlett?
A Volkswagen Polo.
A Polo?
Yeah.
Those are pretty small cars.
It's a three-door.
Oh.
It's a hatchback.
Yeah.
No.
How is it three doors?
Wait.
How is it three doors without being a hatchback?
Where the third door is like the back door.
There is no back door.
Yeah.
The trunk.
The boots.
It's called the boot.
The boot and the bonnet.
Yes.
Okay.
No.
Why do you call it a three-door?
It's a two-door.
In England, no.
We call it a three-door or a five-door.
Really?
Yeah.
They kind of use that same terminology in America.
Because it is a three-door.
Really?
I've always heard it as a two-door or a four-door.
Yeah.
I have a five-door.
Well, good for you.
I don't have a car.
I interrupt us there.
Guess what, guys?
Look at me.
How do you guys have a car?
I don't have a car.
You're poor.
We're rich.
Yeah.
I guess that's it.
My car's in England.
It's not in Shanghai.
No.
I don't have a car in Shanghai either.
You have cars in other countries, even more exotic.
Yeah.
Look at you guys.
Well, she...
I have a secret that I'm not supposed to tell anybody.
What's the secret?
I can't tell anybody.
No.
The scarlet is really famous.
She's famous.
Yeah.
Because she's not famous here.
She's famous, like, in places like Bangladesh.
She's got a few hit singles there.
Iceland.
Nice.
Canada.
Canada's not really on that small of a place.
Alberta.
And so that's why she's got cars all over the world.
I see.
And that's why I'm in China.
She's hiding from the paparazzi.
Secret.
But now, I've let it all go.
Like, all Bill has.
So I'm going to have to move again.
That's another reason I'm moving from Chinese politics.
See?
I'm going to have to move her cover.
Yep.
Okay.
So that's going on on Monday.
We're having car trouble.
Actually, the car won't start.
So we're going to go over a couple of different options now.
What is that usually when the car doesn't start?
What do you guys?
It could be the battery.
The battery.
It could be the starter motor.
It could be the alternator.
Which would cause the battery to discharge.
It could be dead.
It could be the ignition.
It could be spark plugs.
It could be.
No, I was not even listening.
It could be that you're key.
It could be you're using the wrong key.
It could be that you're in the wrong car.
You just don't know how to drive, you know?
Yeah.
There's a lot of possibilities.
So look forward to that lesson.
Yeah.
So troubleshooting.
That's how we found out those roms on English.
We just went through the list.
It's just the right computer.
All right.
So on Tuesday, we have our director's cut show.
And we're going to talk about the movie Precious.
Yeah.
I don't know what movie it is.
This is based on the novel Push by Sapphire.
It's a very good film.
Push by Sapphire.
I watched it recently, actually.
That's the author's name.
It's just Sapphire.
Sapphire.
It's just a one-word name.
Yeah.
Got a problem with that?
Like Madonna?
Yeah.
Like Seal?
Like McLovin?
Like Sting?
McLovin?
Yeah.
Actually, it's not...
You're actually right.
I don't think it's very common for authors to have one name.
I think that's the first.
Maybe.
No.
Well, you know.
Well, no.
Unless Seal wrote an autobiography.
Yeah.
Maybe.
In which case I'm all over it.
You're really into Seal?
What happened to his face?
Maybe he talks about it in the movie.
So this movie Precious is really sad.
It's a drama.
Actually, the co-star Monique, she won an Academy Award for Best Supporting Actress.
Really?
Yeah.
This year?
Who does she play in the film?
Precious' mom.
So her mom was kind of a, I don't know, she had a very, she had a couple of different
problems, psychological issues.
She was treated really badly by her husband as well.
Yeah.
But it's interesting because Monique is a comedian.
Is she?
Yeah.
And then she played these very dramatic roles.
She won an Academy Award.
She did it really well actually.
Yeah, she did an amazing job.
So that's going on on Tuesday.
On Wednesday, we're talking, we have an advanced lesson and we're talking about our carbon
footprint.
We're talking about recycling, reducing, reusing.
Very environmentally conscious episode.
We're talking about going green, biodegradable things, compound posts, what is it?
Compost.
Compost, there you go.
Compost piles.
Composting things.
Yeah.
Oh, that sounds excellent.
So it's more of a, we have an interesting dialogue based on this.
Because, you know, Earth Day is coming up, you know, everyone has to...
Hug a tree.
Turn their lights off.
Turn their lights off for an hour.
Yeah.
So, I think March...
Drive backwards.
I think, isn't March like the environmentally friendly month, like isn't there something
going on at the time?
This is the only month we need to care about it.
The other 11 months of the year.
Forget about it.
What do you do, Bill?
Do you recycle?
Yeah.
At home, I do.
In the States, I do.
Yeah.
Because it's against a lot not to.
Is it really?
Yeah.
I think it is.
They just recently passed that law, actually.
Wow.
So, I mean, if you don't recycle, it is illegal, but I mean, enforcement is kind of spotty.
But you can be fine.
Wow.
I was reading something interesting about your city.
Apparently, it's illegal to have aftermarket neon lights under your car.
I think that could be true.
No, it is.
They're really gaudy.
I think that's more of a taste thing.
Yeah, you know, like the Fast and the Furious, all those neon lights under the cars.
So tacky.
Illegal in Seattle.
It's a distraction.
And you know what else is illegal in Seattle?
What?
To hug someone while you're driving.
What did you read?
I swear, I am not lying to you.
This is in the rule book in Seattle.
That really makes sense, though.
Why would you hug someone whilst you're driving?
I don't know.
Maybe you're going through a tough time driving.
While you're driving, you stop, and then you hug someone.
What about if you're in traffic and you're idling?
Yeah, actually.
Can you hug while idling?
Or is it only in motion?
Idling?
Is idling?
Your car is turned on.
You may be in drive, but you're not moving.
You're not moving.
You're not in motion.
I think you have to be in motion.
Okay.
I think.
I'll go back.
I'll go home and do some tests for you.
Actually, I also learned that it's not against the law to give a policeman the finger.
In Seattle?
Yes.
How do you know so much about Seattle?
I was reading about it last night.
I was bored.
Really?
Just about Seattle?
Yeah, I found a news article about Seattle in a Seattle local newspaper, and then I was
like, okay, let's read some more.
And then there was like this whole question and answer part in this newspaper.
And it's just.
Seattle Times?
No, it was another Washington.
I think it was a Washington Post.
That's Washington, D.C.
D.
No, no, no, no.
It wasn't the Washington Post then.
But it was another one.
It was in Washington.
It was in Washington State.
I feel so honored that you took the time to read about my phone.
I thought about you when I was reading about Seattle.
I don't know anything about Ecuador.
You should read about it.
You're from Los Angeles anyways.
That doesn't count though.
You should still read about it.
You don't know any other Ecuadorians.
What?
Do you?
I don't know.
No, I don't think so.
I'm the only Ecuadorian.
I know your brother.
Damn it.
Scarlett, I'm the only Ecuadorian Scarlett knows.
I do.
You are.
I mean, you are.
I do know you.
I haven't.
We're not at that point yet, Scarlett.
Sorry, I'm getting way ahead of myself.
It's daydreaming though.
Daydreaming.
Okay, so that's going on on Wednesday, and on Friday we have a very interesting
lesson.
What is it?
I want to know.
Tell me right now.
All about facial hair.
Oh, this is interesting.
This is interesting.
It fascinates me.
Because you can't grow any.
I can grow facial hair.
I thought you said you couldn't.
It just doesn't look all that great.
But you can grow a mustache.
I have a picture of me with an attempted mustache.
Really?
How did it go?
Oh, I need to see that.
It's in my pocket actually.
Is it really?
Will this be a first in the English pod where we pass around a photograph and talk
about it?
Yes.
You just can't see it.
It's actually really important.
You've got a picture of yourself.
It's really embarrassing because it's on my license.
It's a really embarrassing picture and it makes me laugh every time I see it.
We might scan your license and just place it.
Let me see this.
What is going on there?
How long did that take you to grow?
The thing is, if I had normal colored facial hair, it would totally show up as a normal
mustache.
But the thing is, I've got a lot of red in my mustache, so you can't see it.
It kind of looks like you were eating chocolate.
Yeah.
It's like a little stain on my lip.
That's generally how it comes.
You put your mouth against an exhaust pipe.
I was a little bit chubbier back then, too.
You were a little bit chubbier back then.
William Timothy Wynn.
It's not the most flattering.
Timothy!
5-9-1-1-111.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Ignore that, everybody.
Kirkland, Washington.
Okay, well, that's my entire address.
Go, School Cam.
Go, Stockville.
Okay, so actually, you know what?
You have a mustache, you have a beard.
I can maybe grow a goatee, what do you think?
There's a neck beard.
I think you should do that.
Go with it.
How about a soul patch?
No, don't do that.
Yeah, do the soul patch.
Why not?
What's wrong with the soul patch?
Maybe I can grow the extended sideburns.
Mutton chops.
No, not the mutton chops.
Kind of like a...
Just like a long...
Like a chin strap.
Chin strap.
I can maybe pull off a chin strap.
You're just not a chin strap kind of guy.
I think you're either a full beard dude or like how you're presented now.
But it's in like clean shaven.
Yeah.
Or grow just a neck beard.
Can you do that?
Neck beard?
Just neck beard.
Wow, all these types of bits.
I never realized.
Isn't that crazy?
That's what this lesson is all about.
Goatee, what about...
What is it called when you just have like the mustache and the chin hair?
Like a...
A handlebar?
No, a handlebar is when you have the mustache connected to your sideburns going up.
No, a handlebar is just like where the waxed edge is and then, you know, like the flying...
No, no, handlebars go down, right?
Well, what's this then?
That's a French mustache.
That's not a French mustache.
What about a...
Mutton chops are extended sideburns.
And they're kind of fat at the end.
And they're fat at the end, right?
How about the Chuck Norris?
I think that's what you're talking about.
No, Chuck Norris had like the...
The what?
I don't know.
Maybe he didn't.
I don't know what that's called.
Actually, I don't know.
I'm not gonna...
I don't want to message Chuck Norris' facial hair.
Do you like guys with facial hair, Scarlett?
No.
Does it feel nice on your skin?
It feels like they've got something to hide.
It's just...
No.
Really?
So you think guys that have beards are suspicious?
Yeah, dodgy.
Dodgy.
Don't you think it's a sign of maturity?
I'm sorry for everybody who's got beards.
No?
Don't you think it's a sign of maturity?
No.
I just don't like it.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, Jason...
Jason's got a beard.
Goatee.
You think he's dodgy?
He's hiding something under there.
He's hiding something.
He finally is.
Look at him.
He's a very dodgy dog.
Oh my god.
Is he saying that Jason is dodgy because he's got a beard?
Yeah, I am.
He is.
Look at him.
He's really, really...
He has something to hide.
He's not hiding anything on top, though.
I don't think he's hiding.
He looks a little suspicious.
I wouldn't want to cross him with a dark alley.
I don't know.
Well, we'll let you guys know how this whole facial hair thing works out.
I think Bill should try to grow some facial hair for this lesson's sake.
It'll take me a little bit longer than that.
Next time I come and visit you guys, I expect to see a mustache.
Okay, well, last time, the best mustache I ever had consisted of clippings from my own
head.
What?
And pasted to my lip with toothpaste.
Why did you do that?
Just to take pictures of it.
It's really cool, though.
Good times.
You should just have like painted something on there.
No, no, because it's your real hair, so it looks really good.
It looks good.
I doubt that hair stuck on your face with toothpaste looks good.
Is that where that toothpaste came from?
I do that every morning.
No, no, no, no, no.
Well, Marco, you're a Latino fella.
You should have a big fat mustache at least.
I'm not really into mustaches.
I feel like it's a pretty popular thing among Latino men, mustaches, facial hair in general.
Mustaches in particular.
Not really.
When you're young, not really.
Maybe you shave when you're young, and then when you get older to show.
When's the cutoff?
When's the date?
I think maybe 30.
30?
Yeah.
Oh, you're fast, fast, rapidly approaching that.
I am.
Yes, I am.
You're absolutely right.
Thanks for reminding me.
You're working on that mustache.
You're closer to 30 than he is.
Forever young, baby.
All right, so that's everything coming up next week.
A lot of interesting lessons.
Be sure to check them out.
And of course, if you have any lesson suggestions, maybe you guys want to talk about a specific
topic.
I know we had a lesson suggestion about train stations.
I think the user was meaning going to the train station, buying tickets, talking about
the train.
Sure, that'd be useful.
That would be useful.
So we're working on that.
So we are more than open to more suggestions.
We want to hear from you.
So come to EnglishPod.com.
We'll see you guys next time.
Yeah, I just want to say thank you to Scarlett for all the hard work she's put in.
It's been a pleasure.
It's been a real pleasure.
Basically, I share a table with Bill and I have to look at him every day.
So I'm going to miss that.
Scarlett has been quite an experience.
This is a nice, touching moment we're having here at EnglishPod.
Thanks, Bill.
I didn't realize he cared so much.
Thank you, Scarlett.
I know.
I didn't know he cared so much either.
I hope you're this upset when I leave.
When are you leaving?
I don't know.
No, just kidding.
All right.
Bye, guys.
Bye.
EnglishPod.com.
Scarlett, for you to leave.
Bye.